Master Masachika.
Ayano.
What's the matter?
I'm sorry to bother you suddenly.
May I have a moment of your time?
Sure.
Thank you.
This way, please.
She's still the same,
just like a ninja.
Master Masachika,
thank you for your precious...
No need for this.
What is it?
Forgive my rudeness.
Well then.
Master Masachika,
I heard that you're running
for president with Mistress Kujou.
May I know if this is true?
Yes.
The head of the family is
very upset about this.
Why is Master Masachika,
who abandoned the Suou family,
still getting in Mistress Yuki's way?
The head of the family was furious
when he said that.
That old geezer.
He told me not to think of myself
as a Suou after I left that house
and also not to tell anyone
that I'm Yuki's older brother.
But now he's treating me
like a family member?
Don't mess with me, old geezer.
So?
Did he send you
to find out my true intentions?
No, this is my own will.
As Mistress Yuki's retainer,
if someone opposes her,
I must determine
the other party's true intentions.
You sure are loyal.
Are you a samurai?
I have always believed
that Master Masachika
would never do anything
to make Mistress Yuki sad.
Could it be that I was mistaken?
I didn't decide to join the election
to go against Yuki.
It's just that
I ended up becoming Yuki's opponent.
Regardless of the order,
the fact that you're opposing her
doesn't change.
For Master Masachika,
is running with Mistress Kujou
so important that you can betray
Mistress Yuki and even hurt her?
Yes.
I'll do my best to help Alya
become the student council president.
I made a promise to her.
Does that stem from some special emotions?
Could it be that you have feelings...
No.
I'm doing this because I want to.
So please relay this to Grandpa.
Don't blame Yuki for this.
If you have any complaints,
say it to me directly.
As you wish.
Please allow me to ask one last thing.
Master Masachika,
have your feelings for Mistress Yuki
remained unchanged?
To me, Yuki is
the most important person in the world.
Even now, that's how I feel.
So, do me a favor.
Please support her well.
As you wish.
I'm glad to hear your thoughts,
Master Masachika.
I shall take my leave now.
Or did I disappoint her?
Ta-da!
Look, it's this week's
gravure magazine cover!
Hey, Masachika. Who's your favorite?
To be honest,
I don't know anything about idols.
Don't talk like an old man.
Just look at their appearance.
Let me see.
Well, if I had to choose one of them,
it'd be her, I guess.
The girl Masachika picked
kind of resembles Mariya.
Is that so?
Now that you mention it,
she does look like her.
Masachika, is Mariya your type?
No, no like that...
Besides, Masha has a boyfriend.
So if she didn't, would you go after her?
By the way,
when did you start using her nickname?
Aren't you getting too close to her?
No, it's just a coincidence.
I've never looked at Masha that way.
Beast.
You're a member of the student council.
Do you think you can bring that to school?
Well, that's...
Strictly speaking,
Takeshi brought this here.
Then, tell him not to.
Okay.
Let me change the question.
Have you ever thought about dating Suou?
No, I can never date her.
Why?
You're asking me why...
In any case,
if I'm going to date,
I'd like someone I can be friends with.
In other words,
someone like me?
Masachika?
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Right.
Also, girls with cute smiles
are charming too.
People who don't smile with their eyes
do seem unapproachable.
Indeed, their everyday attitude is
really important.
You should be more considerate.
Alya will get hurt.
-What?
It's okay.
I have friends anyway.
I don't mind being unlikeable.
Anyway, make up for it. Hurry up.
Okay.
However!
It doesn't matter when it comes
to a beautiful girl like Princess Alya.
-You suck!
What?
So is that
how you have always viewed me?
I'm truly sorry.
I'm just a cold and unlovable girl,
who only has her looks to offer.
No, you're not that bad.
I'd better confiscate
this magazine.
Come in.
Excuse me.
So, are you satisfied now?
Yes.
Sure enough, Master Masachika is
still the esteemed
Master Masachika I admire.
I'm glad to hear that.
What did my brother say?
Master Masachika said
that he hadn't changed his mind
about running with Mistress Kujou.
I thought so.
Also,
he asked me to relay this
to the head of the family.
"If you have any complaints,
say it to me directly."
Well, that's...
How bold of him.
It seems you're serious too, brother.
Yes.
Such a wonderful spirit
makes my uterus tremble.
Really? Even your uterus is trembling?
Yes.
Excuse me.
Just to be clear,
Ayano, you're not in love
with my brother, are you?
I'm not.
Just as I respect
and admire Mistress Yuki,
I feel the same about Master Masachika.
I have no romantic feelings for him.
Is that so?
I don't have
the arrogant thought like
"I want to be his girlfriend."
As long as I can be used as a tool,
I'm satisfied.
You're just an ordinary Super M,
aren't you?
I'm very sorry.
What does "Super M" mean?
What?
It means Super Maid.
The abbreviation is Super M.
Thank you for the compliment.
It's my honor.
I'll continue to work hard
to become a great Super M.
You just said something amazing.
Right.
There's one last thing.
What is it?
Master Masachika said
that Mistress Yuki is
still the most important person
in the world to him.
Mistress Yuki?
That was close!
I almost shout out my love for my brother
in the center of the school premises!
Good grief.
I can't stand my cute brother.
Anyway...
he's actually serious
about competing with me.
Not bad.
Things are getting interesting.
To be honest,
Alya alone is no match for me.
Most of the freshmen seem to think
that Mistress Yuki will be elected.
As for Mistress Kujou,
to be honest...
"A transfer student who doesn't know
President Suou from junior high school
is doing something reckless."
That's everyone's impression of her.
How merciless.
Well then,
how will my brother turn the tables?
You look very happy.
Indeed, I am.
After all, this is my chance
to have a showdown
with my genius brother
who's also a Suou family prodigy.
I could never beat my brother
no matter what I did.
But now, he's going to challenge me
with this strong partner, Alya.
I'm so excited.
They are worthy opponents.
All right, I'll do my best to defeat them.
By the way, Ayano.
What is it, Mistress Yuki?
Don't you think I look like
the final boss right now?
STUDENT COUNCIL OFFICE
Raise.
Fold. I won't call.
Really?
Actually, I have a high card.
I was right to bluff just now.
What?
Oh my, Alya.
You were so close.
Sure enough,
Suou's skills are far superior.
That kind of psychological warfare is
Yuki's forte, after all.
That's part of it,
but it's mainly because
Alya is too easy to read, right?
Sarashina.
You voiced my hidden thoughts
that I dare not express.
What?
I'm kind of sorry.
Alisa unexpectedly wears
her heart on her sleeve.
I thought she was less emotional
than her sister.
Maybe Mariya is the one
who's harder to read.
That's true.
To be honest,
I can't figure her out either.
She's basically a good kid like Madonna.
But sometimes, her words
and actions are strange.
Masha does have a unique sensibility.
Like, a bit off?
You voiced my hidden thoughts again!
I'm sorry.
Mistress Sarashina.
Would you like something to drink?
You're good at hiding your presence.
I'm fine.
There's still some left.
I see.
By the way, is this behavior and conduct
something you must learn
as Suou's retainer?
Yes.
I learned it from my grandparents.
Ayano's grandparents
used to work for Yuki's family.
So, your parents too?
No, my parents are office workers.
I see.
I became a retainer
because I admired my grandparents,
not because it's a family business.
By the way, when did you
start being a retainer?
I don't know exactly when I started,
but I decided to become a retainer
when I was in second grade.
That's too early.
That's how much I admired my grandparents.
And
Masa...
It just so happened
that Mistress Yuki was the perfect master.
Ayano, come here.
I'm sorry.
I misspoke just now, Master Masachika.
It's fine. You just need to be careful.
It's just...
RESPECT AND ADMIRATION
She has such determined eyes!
Why?
Is she not angry anymore?
When did my likeability increase?
Is doing things quietly
another skill as a retainer?
Yes.
My grandparents always told me
that as a servant,
I had to work hard to become air.
Ayano.
Can you pour me some juice too?
Forgive my negligence, Mistress Mariya.
Alya just scolded me for being annoying.
Hey, is this going to be okay?
They won't fight, right?
I think they'll be fine.
Alya seems to be enjoying it.
It looks like she's having fun.
That's rare.
You're right.
Oh, you can tell?
I can tell.
Having fun?
That expression?
Oh my, is it finished?
I'll go buy some more.
Then, I...
It's okay.
Ayano, you're the heroine today.
After all, you and I are the protagonists
of this welcome party.
As a girl, you're naturally the heroine.
That's right.
Well, hero,
please escort me.
Why?
WELCOME PARTY
FOR NEW STUDENT COUNCIL MEMBERS
I'm going to buy some drinks.
What do you want?
I want café au lait.
Not the white one, the brown one.
I want red bean soup.
I want soda.
I want cola...
No, ginger ale.
I'll just have water.
Well then, I want lemon tea.
Masha, you don't have to tell me, right?
We're going together.
Right.
Well,
so soda, ginger ale, lemon tea,
and brown café au lait,
as well as red bean soup
and water. Got it.
-What?
Kuze,
thank you once again.
Why did you suddenly say that?
Thank you for running
for student council president with Alya.
I'm sure Alya is overjoyed about it.
It's nothing much.
And there's no need for you to thank me.
My goodness.
Of course, I should thank you.
Alya had no one to lean on all this time.
There's finally someone
willing to support her.
Are you...
It's nothing.
I was just thinking, Masha.
Are you purposely hiding
your serious side from Alya?
Well,
I don't want to compete with Alya.
Because Alya is a very serious child.
She tries her best in everything she does.
I really like Alya the way she is.
What are you doing?
Is that why
you're playing the role
of a meek older sister?
I'm not pretending.
It's tiring to be tensed up
all the time, right?
You need to relax.
But
I don't deny that I tend to be meek
in front of Alya.
Because...
I don't want Alya to be alone.
It's not just sisters.
Siblings have
a very complicated relationship.
They're closer than anyone else,
but because of that,
they can't help
but have a sense of rivalry.
Yes.
I feel the same way.
The reason
I don't feel inferior to Yuki is
all thanks to her always brazenly saying
that she loves her brother the most.
CAFÉ AU LAIT
Yuki's eccentric personality
with a strong otaku vibe...
Is she also playing
the role of a silly little sister?
No, I'm sure that's her true self.
Masha,
you're such a good sister.
Yes.
I may not look like it,
but I'm a good sister.
Keep what we discussed
a secret from Alya.
I won't tell her.
Even if I did, she wouldn't believe
that her own sister is
so serious and mature.
Oh dear.
Aren't you hiding
your serious side as well?
The reason I'm doing this isn't
as impressive as yours.
I'm just doing it for my sake.
I just want to live an easy life
so I'm playing a frivolous character
to avoid anyone from relying on me.
Please don't mind me.
There, there.
You're doing your best.
It's okay.
I'm sure you'll be fine, Kuze.
I didn't...
You're a boy, after all.
You're amazing.
I wonder why.
When I face Masha,
I can't help but let my guard down.
Alisa Kujou.
Sorry for the sudden visit.
I'm Sayaka Taniyama from Class F.
Do you have a minute?
Sayaka Taniyama.
I remember that in junior high,
she competed with Yuki for the presidency.
Kujou.
Are you really going to join
the presidential election with Kuze?
Yes. What's the matter?
To actually do something so vulgar,
aren't you ashamed?
What?
You stole the person
who Suou wanted to invite as her partner.
Are you causing trouble?
What?
What do you mean?
Are you saying I used dirty tricks
to get Kuze on my side?
Didn't you?
I don't know how you did it,
but you chose that pathetic Kuze
as your partner
to make Suou angry, didn't you?
I didn't!
Alya? Taniyama?
What's happening here?
I don't know either.
She suddenly came to pick a fight,
saying I played dirty
to steal you from Suou.
What's going on?
Well, Taniyama.
I don't know who told you what,
but I decided to partner
with Alya on my own.
I can't believe it.
As someone who's utterly pathetic,
why would you team up
with that transfer student?
Wait, you're calling me pathetic.
Well, I won't deny it.
Anyway,
Yuki acknowledges this too.
It's all your misunderstanding.
Since your words have offended Alya,
could you please apologize?
I see.
So you're the one
who should be punished, right?
Kuze.
I'm calling a general meeting
to challenge you.
What?
Did you hear that?
She's calling a general meeting.
Seriously?
What's going on?
A presidential candidate
is calling a general meeting.
No, wait a minute.
Are you serious?
Do you think I'd joke about this?
I'm going to kick you out
of the presidential election.
No.
I'll kick you out of the student council.
Hold on.
Election candidates holding a general
meeting will affect their standing, right?
You can't ignore me.
Can you not decide on your own?
The eye-candy presidential candidate
who only has good grades should stay out.
What?
We're a pair in the presidential election.
As a fellow presidential candidate,
if you want to defeat Kuze,
let me take you on.
And here I thought I was sparing you.
Fine.
I'll crush both of you together.
People like you aren't cut out
for the presidential election.